<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<webpage lastModified="$Date$" id="dozbib">
 <title xml:lang="de">Willkommen bei der Universitätsbibliographie der UDE</title>
 <title xml:lang="en">Welcome to Bibliography of UDE</title>
 
 <section class="highlight1" xml:lang="de">  
   <h3>Die Universitätsbibliographie</h3>
    <p>
    der Universität Duisburg-Essen ist der <strong>zentrale Publikationsnachweis</strong> der Hochschule, der als Online-Dienst tagesaktuell und zeitnah die 
    Publikationstätigkeit der Hochschulangehörigen verzeichnet.
    </p>     
    <p>
    Die Einträge der Bibliographie beruhen großenteils auf den Angaben der Autoren selbst, seit September 2010 überarbeitet und vervollständigt ein Redaktionsteam die Neueinträge.     
    </p>    
    <h3>
    Sie sind Angehöriger der Universität Duisburg-Essen</h3> 
    <p>und möchten Ihre Publikationen in der Universitätsbibliographie nachgewiesen haben?</p>    
    <p>
    <a href="../newPublication.xed">Hier können Sie Ihre Publikation an die Universitätsbibliographie melden</a>
    </p>
  </section>
  <section class="highlight1" xml:lang="en">   
    <h3>The University Bibliography</h3> 
    <p>
    of Duisburg-Essen University is the <strong>central resource</strong> of the university that chronicles all the publication activities of the university members and provides 
    online service that is updated daily and in real time.
    </p>    
    <p>
    The bibliography entries are based mainly on the information provided by the authors themselves, since september, 2010 an editoral team revises and completes the new entries.     
    </p>    
    <h3>
    You are a member of Duisburg Essen University</h3> 
    <p>and would like to chronicle your publications in the university library?</p>    
    <p>
    <a href="../newPublication.xed">Here you can register your publication at the university bibliography</a>
    </p>
  </section>
  
  <section class="highlight2">
  <table>
        <tr>
          <td>
            <editor id="gotoUBO-DE">
               <target type="servlet" name="GoToServlet" method="post" format="name=value" />
              <components root="root-gotoUBO-DE">
                <panel id="root-gotoUBO-DE" lines="off">
                  <hidden var="type" default="biblio" />
                  <cell row="1" col="1" anchor="WEST">
                    <text>
                      <label xml:lang="de">Suche</label>
                      <label xml:lang="en">Search</label>
                    </text>
                  </cell>
                  <cell row="1" col="2" anchor="WEST" var="id">
                    <textfield width="25" />
                  </cell>
                  <cell row="1" col="3" anchor="WEST">
                    <submitButton class="roundedButton">
                      <label xml:lang="de">finden</label>
                      <label xml:lang="en">find</label>
                    </submitButton>
                  </cell>
                </panel>
              </components>
            </editor>
          </td>
        </tr>
 </table> 
 </section>     
    
</webpage>
